Finding Aid for the Eiko Ishioka papers LSC.2288
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 11: Audiovisual and born-digital material, 1965-2012
  - Subseries 11.4: Born-digital, 1985-2011; 285 optical discs (CDs and DVDs with PSD, JPG, TIFF, MOV, VOB, and PDF files, among others); 3 floppy disks; 1 zip disk
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0034 (Box 262)
      Selection of images from the book related to Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters and Tokyo: Form & Spirit.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0035 (Box 262)
      Photographs of Tokyo: Form & Spirit art installation and set designs and photographs of M. Butterfly.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0036 (Box 262)
      Photographs of M. Butterfly and L'Inhumaine.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0037 (Box 262)
      Film stills and costume design drawings for Bram Stoker's Dracula, as well as images of posters for the film's release in Japan.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0038 (Box 262)
      Photographs of costumes from Bram Stoker's Dracula.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0039 (Box 262)
      Photographs of costumes for Bram Stoker's Dracula.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0040 (Box 262)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0041 (Box 262)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0042 (Box 262)
      Images of drawings of David Copperfield's magic tricks and one photograph of Dracula's gown in Bram Stoker's Dracula.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0043 (Box 262)
      Photograph of Dreams & Nightmares.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0044 (Box 262)
      Photographs of The Ring of the Nibelung and Chushingura.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0045 (Box 262)
      Images of sets and costume designs from The Ring of the Nibelung and Chushingura.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0046 (Box 262)
      Photographs from The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0047 (Box 262)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0048 (Box 262)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0049 (Box 262)
      Images of costume pieces from The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0050 (Box 262)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0051 (Box 262)
      Costume design sketches and photographs of The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0052 (Box 262)
      Photographs and costume design sketches for characters from The Ring of the Nibelung and from The Cell.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0053 (Box 262)
      Photographs of costumes from The Cell.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0054 (Box 262)
      Photographs of Carl Stargher character in costume from The Cell.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0262_0055 (Box 262)
      Photographic slideshow videos showcasing the uniform design for the opening ceremonies.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0262_0056 (Box 262)
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0262_0057 (Box 262)
    - Stage and moving image projects, uclalsc_2288_0263_0001 (Box 263)
      Video excerpts from The Cell, Closet Land, Bram Stoker's Dracula, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, and Björk's "Cocoon" music video showcasing different costume designs.
    - The Cell, Bram Stoker's Dracula and Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, uclalsc_2288_0263_0003 (Box 263)
      Includes costume designs sketches and photographs.
    - The Sultan's Elephant, uclalsc_2288_0263_0004 (Box 263)
      Video footage for Ishioka's research on the show.
    - Photographs of Ishioka on a trip, uclalsc_2288_0263_0005 (Box 263)
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0263_0006 (Box 263)
      Video footage of athletes parading during the opening ceremonies.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0263_0007 (Box 263)
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0263_0008 (Box 263)
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0010 (Box 263)
      Reference art and images for costume research for Luxor show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0011 (Box 263)
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0012 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men, women and boots for costume research for show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0013 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men, women, boots, and headpieces for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0017 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men, women, animals, headpieces, boots, and people in straight jackets for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0018 (Box 263)
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0019 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men, women, animals, flowers, boots, headpieces, and people in straight jackets for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0020 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men, women, dolls, shoes, fetishes, and monks for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0021 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of rabbits, men, women and children from the late 1800s for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0022 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of rabbits, magicians, a doll, men, women and children from the late 1800's for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0023 (Box 263)
      Costume design sketches for Luxor show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0024 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of women and dolls for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0025 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of magicians, women, groups of people at the beach, and angels for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0026 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men and women from the late 1800s, and of human/animal hybrid creatures for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0027 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of dolls, animal hybrid creatures, and men and women in steampunk attire for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0028 (Box 263)
      Photographs of costumes and set props for Criss Angel's collaboration show with Cirque du Soleil at the Luxor Hotel and a document with meeting minutes related to this project.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0029 (Box 263)
      Storyboard rendering of Cirque du Soleil and Criss Angel collaboration show at the Luxor Hotel.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0030 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of dolls and their clothes, animal hybrid creatures, and men and women from late 1800's for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0031 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of dolls, men, and women (some with masks) for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0032 (Box 263)
      Photographs of women in dresses and of their face makeup for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0033 (Box 263)
      Video footage of Luxor meeting and workshop, which includes behind the scenes look at preparing the scenic elements for the show.
    - Criss Angel Mindfreak, uclalsc_2288_0263_0034 (Box 263)
      Rough cut video footage of Criss Angel's acts, including footage and interviews from his A&E show Criss Angel Mindfreak.
    - Voronin and Svetlana, uclalsc_2288_0263_0035 (Box 263)
      Video footage of different acts by magician and contortion acts.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0263_0036 (Box 263)
      Photographs by Hiroyuki Arakawa of the musical.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0263_0037 (Box 263)
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0039 (Box 263)
      Reference artwork for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0040 (Box 263)
      Various video clips of Ishioka's video research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0041 (Box 263)
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0042 (Box 263)
      Character reference materials for the show, including video and images for Crimson, Criss Angel, Dolls, Human Bird, Kayala's wedding dress, Old Magician, Paparazzi, Poppy, Rabbit, Robot Arm, and Usher.
    - Tokyo Eiko Party, uclalsc_2288_0263_0043 (Box 263)
      Pictures from a party in Tokyo on 2005 January 9, at which Ishioka appears to give an informal speech along with a few others.
    - Eiko International Design Conference presentation, uclalsc_2288_0263_0046 (Box 263)
      Selection of images for slides showcasing work for Apocalypse Now, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, Dreams & Nightmares, Closet Land, Chushingura, Tutu, The Ring of the Nibelung, The Cell, M. Butterfly, Bram Stoker's Dracula, Varekai, "Cocoon", and the Canadian team's uniforms for the 2002 Winter Olympics.
    - Eiko International Design Conference presentation, uclalsc_2288_0263_0047 (Box 263)
      Selection of images for slides showcasing work for Tutu, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, and Bram Stoker's Dracula.
    - Eiko International Design Conference presentation, uclalsc_2288_0263_0048 (Box 263)
      Selection of images for slides showcasing work for Tutu, Varekai, and The Cell.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0049 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men, women, dolls, and flowers for costume research for the show.
    - Luxor, uclalsc_2288_0263_0050 (Box 263)
      Photographs and drawings of men, women, dolls, straight jackets, and masks (many of which are from or inspired by the style of the late 1800s) for costume research for the show.
    - "From Circus to Opera" lectures at Tokyo University of the Arts, uclalsc_2288_0263_0052 (Box 263)
      Photographs from a series of lectures presented by Ishioka at Tokyo University of the Arts in 2002.
    - Eiko by Eiko and The Cell, uclalsc_2288_0263_0053 (Box 263)
      Image of book cover and images of costumes from The Cell.
    - "From Circus to Opera" lectures at Tokyo University of the Arts, uclalsc_2288_0263_0054 (Box 263)
      Poster for a series of lectures by Ishioka at Tokyo University of the Arts.
    - Eiko International Design Conference presentation, uclalsc_2288_0263_0055 (Box 263)
      Video presentation showcasing work for Apocalypse Now, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, Dreams & Nightmares, Closet Land, Chushingura, Tutu, The Ring of the Nibelung, The Cell, M. Butterfly, Bram Stoker's Dracula, Varekai, "Cocoon", and the Canadian team's uniforms for the 2002 Winter Olympics.
    - Parco, uclalsc_2288_0263_0057 (Box 263)
      Advertising campaign videos for Parco featuring Faye Dunaway and Dominique Sandra.
    - Research materials for unidentified project, uclalsc_2288_0264_0006 (Box 264)
      Illustrations from Ernst Haeckel's book, The History of Creation.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0264_0007 (Box 264)
      Photographs of Ishioka with Bono and The Edge of U2, in which they appear to be doing promotional work for Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark.
    - Mori Art Museum, uclalsc_2288_0264_0008 (Box 264)
      Title or cover page with "Eiko Ishioka."
    - Criss Angel and Cirque du Soleil Luxor Hotel show, uclalsc_2288_0264_0009 (Box 264)
      Costume and set design research photographs and drawings of dolls and girls playing with dolls from the Victorian era.
    - Stage and moving image projects, uclalsc_2288_0264_0015 (Box 264)
      Images of work for The Cell, Chushingura, M. Butterfly, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, and The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Video montage, uclalsc_2288_0264_0016 (Box 264)
      Video montage of Eiko's work on stage and moving image projects, exhibitions and events, fashion and uniforms, book, periodical, and record cover design.
    - Ishioka's portrait and image of Leni Riefenstahl exhibition, uclalsc_2288_0264_0017 (Box 264)
    - Tariki: Embracing Despair, Discovering Peace book cover design, uclalsc_2288_0264_0018 (Box 264)
      Font, color, and portrait selections for Hiroyuki Itsuki's book.
    - Immortals, uclalsc_2288_0264_0020 (Box 264)
      Costume design sketch for Hyperion's helmet for the film.
    - Photographs from Ishioka's trip to the Basque Country and London, uclalsc_2288_0264_0021 (Box 264)
      Photographs of Ishioka accompanied by two others in an architectural/sculptural tour through Bilbao at the Guggenheim Museum, the Sondica Airport; the Chillida-Leku museum in Gipuzkoa; The British Museum; Ito; and a building by Rafael Moneo.
    - Lecture by Ishioka, uclalsc_2288_0264_0024 (Box 264)
      Video recording of lecture that is likely about Eiko on Stage.
    - Eiko by Eiko and Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0264_0025 (Box 264)
      Images of various projects as well as layouts for the books.
    - Costume design drawings, uclalsc_2288_0264_0027 (Box 264)
      Costume design sketches and web documents.
    - Stage and moving image projects, uclalsc_2288_0264_0028 (Box 264)
      Images of work for Closet Land, Chushingura, M. Butterfly, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, Bram Stoker's Dracula and The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Research materials for unidentified project, uclalsc_2288_0264_0029 (Box 264)
      Paintings, drawings, and photographs from Life Magazine.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0264_0030 (Box 264)
      Photographs from the live production of the musical.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0264_0033 (Box 264)
      Darker version of character design sketches for the musical.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0264_0034 (Box 264)
      Lighter version of character design sketches for the musical.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0264_0035 (Box 264)
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0264_0036 (Box 264)
      Photographs of Ishioka and others at a reception for the debut of the musical production in Berlin.
    - Fishes' Leni Riefenstahl Triangle Two, uclalsc_2288_0508_0001 (Box 508)
      Content related to a graphic design project Ishioka did on Leni Riefenstahl for More magazine in 1979.
      File formats cannot be viewed due to a lack of required software needed to render the files correctly.
    - Photograph of Ishioka and Francis Ford Coppola at Cannes International Film Festival, uclalsc_2288_0508_0002 (Box 508)
    - Fishes' Leni Riefenstahl Triangle Two, uclalsc_2288_0508_0003 (Box 508)
    - Images for unidentified project, uclalsc_2288_0508_0005 (Box 508)
      Images of Princess Diana, a wing, and a sports event.
    - Unidentified Japanese television program, uclalsc_2288_0508_0006 (Box 508)
    - Unidentified Japanese television program about manga artist, uclalsc_2288_0508_0007 (Box 508)
    - Episode of The Professional of the Day, uclalsc_2288_0508_0008 (Box 508)
      Footage from Japanese television show, The Professional of the Day featuring a man who makes fireworks.
    - The Sultan's Elephant, uclalsc_2288_0508_0009 (Box 508)
      Videos pertaining to the show by Royal de Luxe, in which a giant puppet girl wakes up, gets a shower from the Sultan's Elephant and goes to play in the park.
    - 62nd Tony Awards, uclalsc_2288_0508_0010 (Box 508)
    - Unidentified Japanese television program, uclalsc_2288_0508_0011 (Box 508)
    - Episode of Filmania talk-show, uclalsc_2288_0508_0012 (Box 508)
    - Magazine and newspaper articles about Ishioka, uclalsc_2288_0508_0013 (Box 508)
      Image scans of feature stories about Ishioka's work in the 2008 November issue of Soen and Waraku (unsure which issue) magazines; and Shukan NY Seikatsu newspaper issues from 2008-2009.
    - Photographs of flower petals, uclalsc_2288_0508_0014 (Box 508)
    - Eiko Ishioka fax cover page template, uclalsc_2288_0508_0015 (Box 508)
    - Waraku magazine photographs, uclalsc_2288_0508_0016 (Box 508)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0508_0017 (Box 508)
      Images from The Cell, Chushingura, M. Butterfly, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, The Ring of the Nibelung, Dreams & Nightmares, Bram Stoker's Dracula, and Varekai for the book.
    - Waraku magazine photographs, uclalsc_2288_0508_0018 (Box 508)
    - Photographs of various works, uclalsc_2288_0508_0019 (Box 508)
      Photographs and costume designs for work on Björk's "Cocoon" music video, Leni Riefenstahl exhibition, Tutu, the Houston Rockets uniforms, The Fall, and the Olympics.
    - Art Center presentation, uclalsc_2288_0508_0021 (Box 508)
      Selection of images for presentation slides related to design work for Cirque du Soleil's Varekai, Bram Stoker's Dracula, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, and Björk's "Cocoon" music video.
    - Mexico presentation, uclalsc_2288_0508_0022 (Box 508)
      Images selected for slideshow presentation.
    - Mexico presentation, uclalsc_2288_0508_0023 (Box 508)
      Ishioka's speech highlighting aspects of her design career.
    - UCLA Regents' lecture, uclalsc_2288_0508_0024 (Box 508)
      Selection of images by Ishioka showcasing her work for a lecture at UCLA in 2005.
    - UCLA Regents' lecture, uclalsc_2288_0508_0025 (Box 508)
      Promotional flyer materials for lecture
    - I Design book party, uclalsc_2288_0508_0026 (Box 508)
      Photographs of Ishioka and others at a party with a musical performance.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0508_0027 (Box 508)
      Typeface design for the book.
    - Video porfolio showcasing major work, uclalsc_2288_0508_0028 (Box 508)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0508_0029 (Box 508)
    - Eiko Ishioka ggg Books 68, uclalsc_2288_0508_0031 (Box 508)
      Selection of images for the book showcasing various projects.
    - Eiko Ishioka ggg Books 68, uclalsc_2288_0508_0032 (Box 508)
      Selection of images for the book showcasing various design projects, including Apocalypse Now, The Cell, Chushingura, Dreams & Nightmares, Bram Stoker's Dracula, The Ring of the Nibelung, M. Butterfly, Tutu, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, "Cocoon", the 2002 Winter Olympics, package, poster, and magazine designs, as well as work for Parco and Leni Riefenstahl's exhibition.
    - I Design book party, uclalsc_2288_0508_0033 (Box 508)
      Video of Ishioka speaking before an audience during the book launch party. Three other unidentified people speak as well. Also includes footage of two musicians playing music with their biwa and shakuhachi.
    - Eiko Ishioka ggg Books 68, uclalsc_2288_0508_0034 (Box 508)
    - Eiko Ishioka ggg Books 68, uclalsc_2288_0508_0035 (Box 508)
      Book layout mockups including images of various projects for the book.
    - I Design book chapters, uclalsc_2288_0508_0036 (Box 508)
    - Photographs from The Gates party, uclalsc_2288_0508_0037 (Box 508)
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0508_0038 (Box 508)
      Video portfolio of images found in the book.
    - Photographs from The Gates party, uclalsc_2288_0508_0039 (Box 508)
    - Video of Eiko speaking, uclalsc_2288_0508_0040 (Box 508)
    - "100 Questions for Eiko Ishioka" document, uclalsc_2288_0508_0041 (Box 508)
      One hundred questions for Ishioka about her work and habits.
    - I Design book party, uclalsc_2288_0508_0042 (Box 508)
    - Superheroes: Fashion and Fantasy exhibit at The Metropolitan Museum of Art, uclalsc_2288_0508_0043 (Box 508)
      Photographs of Nike costumes on display at the 2008 exhibit.
    - Photographs and video Ishioka's walk through The Gates, uclalsc_2288_0508_0044 (Box 508)
    - Superheroes: Fashion and Fantasy exhibit at The Metropolitan Museum of Art, uclalsc_2288_0508_0045 (Box 508)
      Photographs of outfits on display at the exhibit, including the "Muscle Suit" Descente Ltd. outfit.
    - Photographs and video Ishioka's walk through The Gates, uclalsc_2288_0508_0046 (Box 508)
    - Teresa, el cuerpo de Cristo, Mexico trip, and personal photos, uclalsc_2288_0508_0047 (Box 508)
      Photographs of Ishioka and others on the set of the film, as well as photographs and videos of Ishioka and others celebrating her mom's birthday.
    - Teresa, el cuerpo de Cristo and New Year's Eve celebration, uclalsc_2288_0508_0048 (Box 508)
      Photographs containing a behind the scenes look at Ishioka at work on the set of the film. Also includes personal photographs from New Year's Eve 2006 in Tokyo.
    - Photographs of Ishioka and others celebrating her mother's ninetieth birthday, uclalsc_2288_0508_0049 (Box 508)
    - Björk's "Cocoon" music video and David Copperfield's Dreams & Nightmares, uclalsc_2288_0508_0050 (Box 508)
      Film stills from Björk's "Cocoon" music video and a photograph from Copperfield's act.
    - Gump's San Francisco exhibition, uclalsc_2288_0508_0051 (Box 508)
      Photographs from costumes for exhibition of The Cell, Bram Stoker's Dracula, and The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Apartment studio, uclalsc_2288_0508_0052 (Box 508)
      Photographs of the interior and exterior of an apartment.
    - Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, uclalsc_2288_0508_0053 (Box 508)
      Video footage of a screening of the movie followed by a brief talk by Ishioka and Q&A.
    - Video of an art exhibition curated by Ishioka, uclalsc_2288_0508_0054 (Box 508)
    - I Design and Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, uclalsc_2288_0508_0055 (Box 508)
      Video footage of a talk by Ishioka discussing the book and the movie.
    - I Design and Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, uclalsc_2288_0508_0056 (Box 508)
      Photographs of Ishioka giving a talk about the book and movie.
    - Episode of The Proposal for the Future, uclalsc_2288_0508_0057 (Box 508)
      Video footage of an NHK episode of The Proposal for the Future that contains a brief segment with Ishioka being interviewed.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0508_0058 (Box 508)
      Photographs of Ishioka presenting about the book.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0508_0060 (Box 508)
      Video clips from The Proposal for the Future about the Beijing Olympics, including footage of the opening ceremonies, behind-the-scenes footage leading up to the opening ceremonies, and an interview with Zhang Yimou.
    - NHK video about the making of sake, uclalsc_2288_0508_0061 (Box 508)
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0508_0062 (Box 508)
      Costume design sketches for characters.
    - NHK movie about Akira Kurosawa, uclalsc_2288_0508_0063 (Box 508)
    - Jazz on a Summer's Day, uclalsc_2288_0508_0064 (Box 508)
      Video recording of Jazz on a Summer's Day.
  - Subseries 11.5: Commercial recordings, 1985-2012 (Box 178, Box 245, Box 246, Box 257)
    Commercial CD, DVD, and LaserDisc copies of films, videos, record albums, and stage productions featuring Ishioka's work, and other related material. Films and videos include Bram Stoker's Dracula, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, The Cell, The Fall, Mirror Mirror, Closet Land, Immortals 3D, and Mechanisms of Density: Last Word from Paradise. Stage productions include Chushingura (LaserDisc only), Cirque du Soleil (Varekai), The Ring of the Nibelung, Takemitsu: My Way of Life, and a David Copperfield performance. Items also relate to the Houston Rockets, Beijing Olympics opening ceremony, and Leni Riefenstahl.
    Record albums include Miles Davis' Tutu, Kimiko Itoh's A Touch of Love, and Ronald Shannon Jackson's Red Warrior. Also present are CD singles of Björk's "Cocoon" and DVD compilations of her music videos. LaserDiscs are in box 178.
    Subseries also includes DVD copies of Nike ad directed by Tarsem with Ishioka's mask designs (box 257).
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
- Series 12: Career, 1960-2011
  Material in this series primarily documents Ishioka's career overall and includes publicity photographs of her, portfolios of images from various projects and advertising campaigns, writings, general publicity, awards, and a small amount of correspondence. Also present is material from a number of professional events, art supplies, and some notes and ephemera.